Break the Chain Lyrics
解開枷鎖
詞： Tena Clark
曲： Tena Clark/Tim Heintz
Intro-
I raise my arms to the sky
我向天舉起我的雙手
On my knees I pray
我屈膝禱告
I’m not afraid anymore
我從此不再害怕
I will walk through that door
我將會通過那道門
Walk, dance, rise
跨出、跳舞、站出來吧！
I can see a world where we all live
我看到一個我們共存的世界
Safe and free from all oppression
自由、沒有壓迫的世界
No more rape or incest, or abuse
沒有強暴、亂倫、或虐待
Women are not a possession
女性不是附屬品
You’ve never owned me,
你從不擁有我
don’t even know me
你根本不瞭解我
I’m not invisible,
我不是隱形的
I’m simply wonderful
我非常獨特的
I feel my heart for the first time racing
我第一次感覺我的心跳快速
I feel alive,
我感到生命的活力
I feel so amazing
我感到美好
I dance cause I love
我跳舞因為我有熱情
Dance cause I dream
我跳舞因為我會築夢
Dance cause I’ve had enough
我跳舞因為我受夠了
Dance to stop the screams
我跳舞為了停止嘶吼
Dance to break the rules
我跳舞為了突破傳統
Dance to stop the pain
我跳舞為了制止疼痛
Dance to turn it upside down
我跳舞要讓天翻地覆
It’s time to break the chain, (come on and... x3)
是時候解開枷鎖，(come on and... x3)
Break the Chain
解開枷鎖
Strike
敲響閃舞
Dance, rise
跳舞、站出來吧！
In the middle of this madness, we will stand
在整個混亂當中，我們會堅持我們的立場
I know there is a better world
我知道一個更好的世界正在形成
Take your sisters &amp; your brothers by the hand
握起你兄弟姐妹的手
Reach out to every woman &amp; girl
召集所有的婦女和女孩
This is my body, my body’s holy
這是我的身體，我的身體是聖潔的
No more excuses, no more abuses
沒有藉口容任虐待
We are mothers, we are teachers,
我們是母親，我們也是老師
We are beautiful, beautiful creatures
我們是非常美麗的生物
I dance cause I love
我跳舞因為我有熱情
Dance cause I dream
我跳舞因為我會築夢
Dance cause I’ve had enough
我跳舞因為我受夠了
Dance to stop the screams
我跳舞為了停止嘶吼
Dance to break the rules
我跳舞為了突破傳統
Dance to stop the pain
我跳舞為了制止疼痛
Dance to turn it upside down
我跳舞要讓天翻地覆
It’s time to break the chain, (come on and... x3)
是時候解開枷鎖，(come on and... x3)
Break the Chain , (come on and... x3), Break the Chain
解開枷鎖, (come on and... x3), 解開枷鎖
Rise, Dance
站出來跳舞
Sister won’t you help me, sister won’t you rise x4
姐妹，你支持我嗎？姐妹，興起吧！姐妹，站出來吧！ （x4）
Rise, Dance
站出來跳舞
Sister won’t you help me, sister won’t you rise x4
姐妹，你支持我嗎？姐妹，興起吧！姐妹，站出來吧！ （x4）
This is my body, my body’s holy
這是我的身體，我的身體是聖潔的
No more excuses, no more abuses
沒有藉口容任虐待
We are mothers, we are teachers,
我們是母親，我們也是老師
We are beautiful, beautiful creatures
我們是非常美麗的生物
I dance cause I love
我跳舞因為我有熱情
Dance cause I dream
我跳舞因為我會築夢
Dance cause I’ve had enough
我跳舞因為我受夠了
Dance to stop the screams
我跳舞為了停止嘶吼
Dance to break the rules
我跳舞為了突破傳統
Dance to stop the pain
我跳舞為了制止疼痛
Dance to turn it upside down
我跳舞要讓天翻地覆
It’s time to break the chain, (come on and... x3)
是時候解開枷鎖，(come on and... x3)
Break the Chain , (come on and... x3), Break the Chain
解開枷鎖, (come on and... x3), 解開枷鎖
I dance cause I love
我跳舞因為我有熱情
Dance cause I dream
我跳舞因為我會築夢
Dance cause I’ve had enough
我跳舞因為我受夠了
Dance to stop the screams
我跳舞為了停止嘶吼
Dance to break the rules
我跳舞為了突破傳統
Dance to stop the pain
我跳舞為了制止疼痛
Dance to turn it upside down
我跳舞要讓天翻地覆
It’s time to break the chain, (come on and... x3)
是時候解開枷鎖，(come on and... x3)
Break the Chain , (come on and... x3), Break the Chain
解開枷鎖, (come on and... x3), 解開枷鎖
One Billion Rising
十億人站起來